eduers.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy

## Terms of Use and Privacy Policy for Use of EDUers.com (Effective Date 2/5/2016)

We appreciate your interest in the content and services of EDUers.com. Continue reading to learn about the conditions governing the use of our website, and the way in which EDUers.com gathers and applies different types of information in order to bring you content and related products and services.

By visiting our website, we assume you agree to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy outlined below. Your use is also acknowledgment and agreement that the information we collect on our website may be shared with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties. We do this so you can receive relevant degree information, as well as to inform you of other programs and education-related products and services. Additionally, you acknowledge and agree with our right to release any collected information, personally identifiable or otherwise, as needed, to businesses providing administration services to our company, such as email service delivery.

We may occasionally update our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy in the future. We recommend that you periodically review this page for the most up-to-date practices concerning your privacy and other important information.

## Cookies

Using this website means you acknowledge and consent to our use of cookies.

What are cookies? Cookies are small pieces of data sent from a website and stored in the user's web browser, commonly for technical purposes such as web analytics. We perform our web analytics mainly using Google Analytics, a Google, Inc. tool. Learn more about Google Analytics [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html).

Advertising cookies allow advertisers to show ads more relevant to the user's interests, but do not contain personally identifiable information, so users are still anonymous. Advertising cookies, sometimes referred to as third-party cookies, track navigation and publish ads on behalf of third parties.

We use cookies, including those through services and partnerships with vendors and third party service providers, in the following ways: 1) as part of a web analytics efforts to capture demographic and other anonymous data for web optimization and other analysis; 2) for "lead auditing," which is a process of ensuring the accuracy, relevance and validity of submitted information that is submitted; and finally, 3) for the purpose of tracking marketing and conversion, including, but not limited to, targeting and optimizing digital ad serving for improving relevance, user experience, and advertising effectiveness. 

You can remove cookies at any time by going to your browser settings. This may be required on a per-use and not a one-time basis. You can generally opt out of receiving personalized ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or those who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles, as well as from other third party advertisers and ad networks.

You may unsubscribe from these ads by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website.

## Information Collecting

When you submit personal information to EDUers.com, you give permission to us and our affiliated entities -- including schools, third party marketing partners and vendors -- to contact you via telephone, text messages, email, or mail to provide information, marketing or otherwise, for education-related services and products. This action also grants us, our affiliates, and partners and vendors the right to contact you, and it also means you relinquish any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call list or other applicable laws for a period of time. Through your submission, you effectively omit Do Not Call requirements established by state and federal governments and may also provide exemption for us from other applicable laws. You also grant us the right to release your personal information, for example to abide by a subpoena or other legal procedure, or in other instances required by law. We exercise this option when, in good faith, we:

  * Believe it is necessary to preserve our rights
  * Ensure the safety of you or others
  * Explore alleged fraud
  * Reply to a government or legal request, and/or in the instance that EDUers.com enters into a merger, acquisition, or sale of some or all of its assets to a third party

### Submitted Information

We provide web forms for the voluntary submission of personal contact information, including name, telephone number, mailing address and email address. The purpose is to provide the requested services, as well as to match you to an education product or service. We collect your submitted information, then store it and share it with schools and other third parties to provide you with information about schools, programs and education related services, as necessary.

By voluntarily submitting information, you authorize EDUers.com and our affiliated schools and partners to contact you by telephone, text messages, email or mail in accordance with all applicable laws regarding education options or related topics. If you receive any email communications from us, a school, or third party and wish to unsubscribe, you can opt out by going to the unsubscribe link in the email. Opting out of an email communication means you will be removed from that sender's future mailings.

### Automatic Information

Whenever you interact with our website, we receive and store certain types of anonymous information, as is standard in the industry. We do this so we can make improvements to EDUers.com and to create a more relevant user experience. We use cookies to collect anonymous data, for example, to aid in analytics, site optimization and for tailored advertising and marketing purposes. Examples of anonymous data include, but are not limited to your:

  * Browser version
  * Operating system version
  * IP address

If you have any questions or concerns about Our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, please use the contact form to communicate with us.
